MUHAMAD ALIAMSYAH FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Jakarta, Indonesia | Phone: 085157664203 | Email: amsyah264@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I have experience in the field of Web Development with a proven history working in the clinic industry. I have programming knowledge about PHP, Laravel, Javascript, JQuery, HTML5, CSS and Bootstrap. Information Techology Development, Innovation, Passionate to share knowledge and inspire others.

EXPERIENCE

PT QBIT, - Jakarta, Indonesia

Full Stack Web Development (Oktober 2022 – Desember 2022)

- Responsible for Web Development.
- Maintenance corporate system & client sytem.
- Development Client System using Typescript with PostgreSQL database.
- Bug fixing.

PT LUMUT KARYA SEJAHTERA, - Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Full Stack Web Development (Mei 2022 – September 2022)

- Responsible for Web Development.
- Maintenance corporate system & client sytem.
- Development Client System using PHP YII2 with PostgreSQL database.
- Bug fixing.

PT VIVAMEDIKA – Jakarta, Indonesia

IT Staff & Development (February 2019 - April 2022)

- Propose and provide IT solutions for business and management problem.
- Responsible for Web Development.
- Infrastructure management.
- Maintenance corporate system & website.
- Responsible for network management.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITAS NUSA MANDIRI (2019 - Present)

Bachelor of Teknik Informatika - GPA 3.5

SKILLS

- Laravel
- PHP
- PostgreSQL
- Mysql
- Javascript
- ReactJs
- JQuery
- Adobe Photoshop

WEBSITE CV

• CV Online